{
  "openingRemarks": "NB: you have to give answers as simplified fractions.",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{17}{3} \\div \\dfrac{95}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "119/285",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [285]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{77}{2}\\right)^3\\)",
      "answer": "456533/8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [8]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{31}{9}\\right)^3\\)",
      "answer": "29791/729",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [729]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-13}{6} \\times \\dfrac{-40}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "260/33",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [33]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{97}{8} \\div 29\\)",
      "answer": "97/232",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [232]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-45}{8} \\div 22\\)",
      "answer": "-45/176",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [176]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{100}{3}\\right)^2\\)",
      "answer": "10000/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [9]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{21}{4} \\times -20\\)",
      "answer": "-105",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [1, 0]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-7 \\times \\dfrac{-1}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "7/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-18}{7} \\div \\dfrac{25}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "-36/175",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [175]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(26 \\div \\dfrac{-83}{10}\\)",
      "answer": "-260/83",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [83]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 \\times \\dfrac{-40}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-40/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{33}{4} \\div \\dfrac{-17}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "-33/17",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [17]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{15}{7} \\times \\dfrac{16}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "80/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [7]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-53 \\div \\dfrac{-63}{10}\\)",
      "answer": "530/63",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [63]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{23}{2} \\div \\dfrac{-14}{9}\\)",
      "answer": "-207/28",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [28]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-35}{12} \\div \\dfrac{-100}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "77/240",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [240]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-79}{5} \\div 73\\)",
      "answer": "-79/365",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [365]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-11}{2} \\times 2\\)",
      "answer": "-11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [1, 0]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{22}{9} \\div \\dfrac{87}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "110/783",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [783]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{9}{4}\\right)^2\\)",
      "answer": "81/16",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [16]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-38}{5} \\times \\dfrac{33}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "-627/10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [10]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-13}{4} \\div \\dfrac{-49}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "65/196",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [196]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-82}{9} \\times \\dfrac{21}{8}\\)",
      "answer": "-287/12",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [12]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-83}{7} \\div \\dfrac{46}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "-913/322",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [322]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{3}{2} \\times \\dfrac{98}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "49",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [1, 0]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(16 \\div \\dfrac{-97}{6}\\)",
      "answer": "-96/97",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [97]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{89}{8} \\div 46\\)",
      "answer": "89/368",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [368]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-17}{2} \\div 60\\)",
      "answer": "-17/120",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [120]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{35}{4} \\times \\dfrac{-43}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "-301/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [4]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-13}{2} \\div \\dfrac{-3}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "65/6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [6]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-49}{12} \\div \\dfrac{11}{6}\\)",
      "answer": "-49/22",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [22]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{32}{5} \\div -91\\)",
      "answer": "-32/455",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [455]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4 \\times \\dfrac{-15}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "-15",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [1, 0]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{15}{11} \\div 9\\)",
      "answer": "5/33",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [33]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-17}{5} \\times \\dfrac{-17}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "289/25",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [25]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{7}{6}\\right)^2\\)",
      "answer": "49/36",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [36]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{48}{5}\\right)^2\\)",
      "answer": "2304/25",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [25]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-29}{3} \\div \\dfrac{-67}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "319/201",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [201]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-7}{5} \\times \\dfrac{49}{6}\\)",
      "answer": "-343/30",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [30]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-67}{12} \\div \\dfrac{13}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "-469/156",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [156]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-23}{2} \\times 31\\)",
      "answer": "-713/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{21}{2} \\div \\dfrac{97}{9}\\)",
      "answer": "189/194",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [194]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-49}{5} \\times \\dfrac{23}{10}\\)",
      "answer": "-1127/50",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [50]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-29}{9}\\right)^2\\)",
      "answer": "841/81",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [81]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{2} \\div \\dfrac{-37}{6}\\)",
      "answer": "-15/37",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [37]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{95}{6} \\times \\dfrac{-51}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "-1615/22",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [22]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{35}{4} \\div \\dfrac{99}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "35/99",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [99]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{11}{2}\\right)^2\\)",
      "answer": "121/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [4]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-90}{11}\\right)^2\\)",
      "answer": "8100/121",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [121]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{57}{7} \\div \\dfrac{-1}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "-57",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [1, 0]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{3}{8}\\right)^2\\)",
      "answer": "9/64",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [64]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-47}{7}\\right)^3\\)",
      "answer": "-103823/343",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [343]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-31 \\times \\dfrac{85}{8}\\)",
      "answer": "-2635/8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [8]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-100}{11} \\times \\dfrac{13}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "-650/11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [11]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{23}{6} \\times \\dfrac{-57}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "-437/8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [8]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{79}{3} \\div \\dfrac{-38}{9}\\)",
      "answer": "-237/38",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [38]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{50}{3} \\div -49\\)",
      "answer": "-50/147",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [147]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{95}{11} \\div -69\\)",
      "answer": "-95/759",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [759]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-69}{11} \\times -40\\)",
      "answer": "2760/11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [11]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{25}{2} \\times \\dfrac{-91}{10}\\)",
      "answer": "-455/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [4]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-10}{3} \\div -14\\)",
      "answer": "5/21",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [21]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-51}{2} \\div \\dfrac{-43}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "102/43",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [43]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-87}{4} \\times \\dfrac{13}{8}\\)",
      "answer": "-1131/32",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [32]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(93 \\div \\dfrac{-33}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "-62/11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [11]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{55}{2}\\right)^2\\)",
      "answer": "3025/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [4]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-25}{3}\\right)^3\\)",
      "answer": "-15625/27",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [27]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{67}{4} \\times -13\\)",
      "answer": "-871/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [4]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{35}{8} \\div \\dfrac{77}{10}\\)",
      "answer": "25/44",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [44]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-67}{8} \\div \\dfrac{33}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "-335/264",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [264]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-25}{2} \\div \\dfrac{-22}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "75/44",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [44]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(3 \\times \\dfrac{-41}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "-123/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [4]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(18 \\times \\dfrac{59}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "531/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{94}{11} \\div \\dfrac{-11}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "-188/121",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [121]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(37 \\div \\dfrac{-23}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-111/23",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [23]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{49}{5}\\right)^3\\)",
      "answer": "117649/125",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [125]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{6}{5}\\right)^3\\)",
      "answer": "216/125",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [125]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(55 \\times \\dfrac{-53}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "-265",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [1, 0]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-94}{9}\\right)^2\\)",
      "answer": "8836/81",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [81]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{3}{5}\\right)^3\\)",
      "answer": "27/125",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [125]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-5}{4} \\div \\dfrac{-78}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "25/312",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [312]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-1}{3} \\div -13\\)",
      "answer": "1/39",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [39]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{6}{7} \\div \\dfrac{83}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "24/581",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [581]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-1 \\times \\dfrac{-48}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "48/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{97}{3}\\right)^3\\)",
      "answer": "912673/27",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [27]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-53}{10}\\right)^2\\)",
      "answer": "2809/100",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [100]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{79}{10} \\div 6\\)",
      "answer": "79/60",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [60]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-34}{9} \\div \\dfrac{85}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "-22/45",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [45]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{47}{7} \\div \\dfrac{-38}{9}\\)",
      "answer": "-423/266",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [266]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-89}{2}\\right)^2\\)",
      "answer": "7921/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [4]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-83}{9} \\div \\dfrac{45}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "-913/405",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [405]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{33}{4} \\div \\dfrac{-14}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "-363/56",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [56]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{42}{11} \\div \\dfrac{85}{8}\\)",
      "answer": "336/935",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [935]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{22}{3} \\times -22\\)",
      "answer": "-484/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5 \\times \\dfrac{92}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "92",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [1, 0]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-11}{3} \\times 27\\)",
      "answer": "-99",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [1, 0]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(9 \\times \\dfrac{-7}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "-63/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{18}{5} \\times \\dfrac{13}{12}\\)",
      "answer": "39/10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [10]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{71}{5} \\times \\dfrac{-1}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "-71/25",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [25]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{2} \\times \\dfrac{-41}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-205/6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [6]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{89}{11} \\times \\dfrac{96}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "8544/55",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [55]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{21}{2} \\) of \\( \\dfrac{97}{8}\\)",
      "answer": "2037/16",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [16]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-95}{12} \\div \\dfrac{-17}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "95/68",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [68]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-42}{5} \\div \\dfrac{-78}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "7/13",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [13]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{22}{7} \\) of \\( \\dfrac{51}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "1122/35",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [35]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-49}{10} \\div \\dfrac{-17}{6}\\)",
      "answer": "147/85",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [85]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{32}{5} \\div \\dfrac{-49}{6}\\)",
      "answer": "-192/245",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [245]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-22}{7} \\times \\dfrac{89}{6}\\)",
      "answer": "-979/21",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [21]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{8}{3} \\) of \\( \\dfrac{19}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "76/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-9}{2} \\div \\dfrac{-47}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "63/94",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [94]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-14}{9} \\div -30\\)",
      "answer": "7/135",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [135]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(75 \\times \\dfrac{-57}{8}\\)",
      "answer": "-4275/8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [8]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-71}{12} \\times \\dfrac{37}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "-2627/48",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [48]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-96}{5} \\times 13\\)",
      "answer": "-1248/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-85}{9} \\div \\dfrac{-3}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "170/27",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [27]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{10}{3} \\div 6\\)",
      "answer": "5/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [9]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-47}{6} \\times \\dfrac{-3}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "47/22",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [22]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{43}{2} \\div \\dfrac{41}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "129/82",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [82]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(34 \\times \\dfrac{-89}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "-1513/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-65}{3} \\times -19\\)",
      "answer": "1235/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [3]
    }
  ]
}
